{
    "id": "2aebee05f1454c0c89621bf7702f3fac",
    "title": "English Vocabulary Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "In the ……………………….. the author states his intentions in writing the book.",
            "description": "Foreword means introduction or preface.",
            "answers": [
                "foreword",
                "foreward",
                "forward"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6126d1c175ea4676a0d21ade931e6b92"
        },
        {
            "question": "The museum curator discovered that the Persian vase was a  ………………………..",
            "description": "Forgery means fake or fraud.",
            "answers": [
                "forge",
                "forage",
                "forgery"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "64740a80dee64ef2902921e9eff39928"
        },
        {
            "question": "It looks like he has …………………………. our appointment.",
            "description": "The past participle of forget can be either forgotten or forgot.",
            "answers": [
                "forgot",
                "forgotten",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2ff9a6c783634123add8e0ae0598bf60"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is so …………………………. that she has to make a note of everything.",
            "description": "Forgetful means absentminded.",
            "answers": [
                "forgetful",
                "forgettable",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3d7c68e0165c40d4a619d8fbfcfd6b12"
        },
        {
            "question": "Because of other expenses, I had to ………………………… that dress.",
            "description": "To forgo is to do without. Forage means fodder.",
            "answers": [
                "forgo",
                "forage",
                "forge"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1cf1340c74a94955a47553b0a56b4591"
        },
        {
            "question": "When I saw that ……………………….. watchdog, I went no further.",
            "description": "Forbidding means dangerous-looking.",
            "answers": [
                "forbidden",
                "forbidding",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a81366814a5b4eb38ab64c0b128229b4"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you ever seen anyone so fond of ……………………………..?",
            "description": "Desserts means sweets.",
            "answers": [
                "deserts",
                "desserts"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7ac61b9d7d864d9a909e180a081e15ac"
        },
        {
            "question": "The child …………………………… about in the water until the lifeguard got to him.",
            "description": "To flounder is to struggle clumsily.",
            "answers": [
                "foundered",
                "floundered"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d80dbecc0f384f2f977efd7130607a10"
        },
        {
            "question": "We know she is rich, so she doesn’t have to …………………………. it.",
            "description": "To flaunt is to show off.",
            "answers": [
                "float",
                "flaunt",
                "flout"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dc4e588acc084b4ea8a6da79afdaf765"
        },
        {
            "question": "That was a …………………………….. abuse of his authority.",
            "description": "Flagrant means shockingly bad or shameless.",
            "answers": [
                "flagrant",
                "fragrant",
                "flagrent"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "290cc1a25d3d471793ac0ca01986938b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The visiting head of state was given a ……………………………. welcome.",
            "description": "Fitting means suitable fitful means sporadic.",
            "answers": [
                "fitting",
                "fitful"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "84e00caf009c46f5a491e459b750cde0"
        },
        {
            "question": "The children get ………………………. when we take them to church.",
            "description": "Fidgety means restive.",
            "answers": [
                "fidgety",
                "fidelity",
                "fidget"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a888d137cee842cc93c9cfe37f87db69"
        }
    ]
}